how?
어떻게?
What and how?
무엇과 어떻게?
Huang Zisheng.
황쯔셩.
We had a great time chatting.
우리는 대화를 나누며 즐거운 시간을 보냈습니다.
I realized
나는 깨달았다
he is
그는
Very cheerful person.
매우 쾌활한 사람.
why do we use
우리는 왜 사용하는가?
A cheerful person?
쾌활한 사람?
Ask the spy.
스파이에게 물어보세요.
They choose it.
그들은 그것을 선택합니다.
if your attitude
당신의 태도라면
to others,
다른 사람에게,
no need
필요 없음
Me becoming a lobbyist?
내가 로비스트가 된다고?
Have you reminded him?
그에게 상기시켜 주셨나요?
Let’s wait and see.
기다리고 보자.
tonight,
오늘 밤,
Not eating yet?
아직 식사 안 했어?
I also have a bowl of instant noodles.
나도 인스턴트 라면 한 그릇을 먹습니다.
I'll get it for you.
내가 가져다줄게.
Your emotional intelligence is very high.
당신의 감성지능은 매우 높습니다.
i will entertain you
내가 당신을 즐겁게 해줄게
Gram.
그램.
Then I'll eat instant noodles.
그럼 저는 라면을 먹을게요.
Han Lie came in.
한리가 들어왔습니다.
Han Lie has accepted it.
Han Lie가 이를 수락했습니다.
New mission letter.
새로운 임무 편지.
This seems to be
이 것 같다
He'll be making new moves soon.
그는 곧 새로운 움직임을 보일 것입니다.
After accepting the mission,
미션을 수락한 후,
Han Lie immediately ordered
한리는 즉시 명령했다
hotel room.
호텔 방.
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
리조트 Pulau Xiaoyue.
Tomorrow evening.
내일 저녁.
registered resident
등록된 거주자
He was alone.
그는 혼자였습니다.
The elevator has arrived.
엘리베이터가 도착했습니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
why don't you take it
왜 가져가지 그래?
CCTV Hotel?
CCTV 호텔?
The identity of the contact is not yet known.
연락처의 신원은 아직 알려지지 않았습니다.
If he hides in a hotel
호텔에 숨어 있으면
There is a risk of being discovered.
발각될 위험이 있습니다.
Why?
왜?
They have to come to the hotel to pick up the goods,
물건을 찾으러 호텔로 와야 하는데,
Still have to stay one night.
아직은 1박을 해야 합니다.
have no idea.
전혀 모른다.
He is very relaxed.
그는 매우 편안합니다.
then,
그 다음에,
When is your vacation?
휴가는 언제인가요?
You should know.
당신은 알고 있어야.
After we broke up,
우리가 헤어진 후,
Don’t you go on vacation anymore?
이제 휴가 안 가시나요?
impossible.
불가능한.
This is not a holiday.
이것은 휴일이 아닙니다.
in this case,
이 경우,
No longer looking for a girlfriend?
더 이상 여자친구를 찾고 있지 않으신가요?
Tanya.
타냐.
just asking.
그냥 물어 보는 건데.
Liu, he's back.
리우, 그가 돌아왔어.
as a child,
어렸을 때,
My home is near here.
내 집이 여기 근처야.
My sister often takes me here.
내 여동생이 나를 여기로 자주 데려가곤 한다.
I'm the one causing this problem.
이 문제를 일으키는 사람은 바로 나입니다.
Where is your sister?
네 여동생은 어디 있어?
My brother can do whatever he wants
형이 원하는 건 뭐든지 할 수 있어
Do better than me.
나보다 더 잘해라.
Only the person who truly loves you
당신을 진심으로 사랑하는 사람만이
who will continue to give to you
누가 너한테 계속 줄래?
Chances of screwing up.
망할 가능성이 있습니다.
perhaps.
아마도.
you
너
tell your sister
네 여동생에게 말해봐
About the game?
게임에 대해서?
impossible.
불가능한.
This is our secret.
이것이 우리의 비밀입니다.
What should I tell him?
그에게 무엇을 말해야 합니까?
He thought I would only bring trouble.
그는 내가 문제만 가져올 것이라고 생각했습니다.
recently,
최근,
This happens.
이런 일이 발생합니다.
Maybe he's right.
어쩌면 그가 옳을 수도 있습니다.
I don't find it funny either.
나도 재미없다고 생각한다.
Just for fun, don't understand the specific situation.
재미삼아 구체적인 상황을 이해하지 못하겠습니다.
Isn't it visible?
눈에 보이지 않나요?
Too hypocritical?
너무 위선적인가요?
exit the game.
게임을 종료합니다.
Are you really not worried at all?
정말 전혀 걱정되지 않나요?
Worry.
걱정하다.
But we can’t sink deeper and deeper.
하지만 우리는 점점 더 깊이 가라앉을 수 없습니다.
but my heart
하지만 내 마음은
Still a little uneasy.
아직도 조금 불안합니다.
Feeling guilty?
죄책감을 느끼시나요?
Can you use nice words?
좋은 단어를 사용할 수 있나요?
and lost?
그리고 길을 잃었어?
We are the victims.
우리는 피해자입니다.
We are stuck.
우리는 갇혀 있습니다.
Two young people tested negative.
청소년 2명은 음성 판정을 받았습니다.
Consoling yourself after making a mistake?
실수한 후에 스스로 위로를 하시나요?
ways to entertain yourself
자신을 즐겁게 하는 방법
Won't come to the beach.
해변에 오지 않을 거예요.
sigh.
한숨을 쉬다.
I can't stand it either
나도 참을 수 없어
Feeling sorry for myself here.
여기서 나 자신에 대해 미안함을 느낀다.
Tomorrow is the weekend,
내일은 주말이에요,
Do you still dare to go crazy?
아직도 감히 미쳐버릴 수 있나요?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
Across oceans.
바다 건너.
Ayo.
아요.
Why doesn't he go to the elevator?
그 사람은 왜 엘리베이터로 가지 않는 걸까요?
Where did he go?
그는 어디로 갔습니까?
The safe path is on the other side.
안전한 길은 반대편에 있습니다.
Batu.
바투.
Ada.
에이다.
decided.
결정했다.
This is a safety line
이것은 안전선이다
Towards the roof.
지붕을 향해.
you check
당신이 확인
Is there anyone else?
다른 사람이 있나요?
To the roof?
지붕으로?
OK
좋아요
It's all over.
모든 끝났어.
No one goes to the roof.
옥상에는 아무도 가지 않습니다.
No receipts, no transactions.
영수증도 없고 거래도 없습니다.
So what can we do on the roof?
그럼 우리는 옥상에서 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
roof?
지붕?
military base.
군사 기지.
Hang Lie is back.
행 라이가 돌아왔습니다.
Come on, go up and have a look.
자, 올라가서 한번 보세요.
Do you think this signal tower
이 신호탑이 생각나나요?
Is there anything special?
특별한 것이 있나요?
Opposite is the military headquarters.
맞은편에는 군 사령부가 있습니다.
There is a host.
호스트가 있습니다.
There is a hard drive here.
여기에 하드 드라이브가 있습니다.
There is a hard drive.
하드 드라이브가 있습니다.
Be sure to have a camera.
카메라를 꼭 가지고 가세요.
The camera is here.
카메라는 여기 있어요.
Extraordinary.
기이한.
There's a military base lurking here.
여기에 군사 기지가 숨어 있습니다.
is the best view.
최고의 전망이다.
This signal tower is built here.
이 신호탑이 여기에 세워졌습니다.
There must be something wrong.
뭔가 문제가 있는 것 같아요.
Han Lie stood up again.
한리는 다시 일어섰다.
Ayo.
아요.
feels like my life
내 인생 같은 느낌
A new chapter will begin.
새로운 장이 시작됩니다.
what are you kissing
너 뭐 키스하는 거야?
don't you think
너는 생각하지 않니?
full
가득한
About to run
실행 예정
Feel the peak of life?
인생의 절정을 느껴보세요?
Young people like to fantasize, and that's a good thing.
젊은 사람들은 환상을 좋아하는데 그것은 좋은 일입니다.
This is where?
여기가 어디야?
Play with this.
이것을 가지고 놀아보세요.
Yes.
예.
how?
어떻게?
Do you dare to play big?
감히 큰 플레이를 하시겠습니까?
How old?
몇 살?
In one round, everything is at stake.
한 라운드에서는 모든 것이 위태로워집니다.
stop.
멈추다.
Don't dare.
감히하지 마십시오.
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
Ayo.
아요.
You think, this round
이번 라운드에는
Do we win or lose?
우리가 이기나요, 지는가요?
I won.
내가이 겄어.
I bet I lost.
내가 졌다고 장담한다.
Who lost the bet?
누가 내기에서 졌나요?
Very unfortunate.
매우 불행한 일입니다.
I won the bet, and I also won the other party.
내기에서도 이겼고, 상대방도 이겼습니다.
OK
좋아요
If you can really win
정말 이길 수 있다면
Let me tell you a secret.
한 가지 비밀을 말씀드리겠습니다.
if i win,
내가 이기면,
I also have to tell you a secret.
나도 당신에게 비밀을 말해야 해요.
agree.
동의하다.
What's the stakes?
스테이크는 무엇입니까?
I can bet.
내기할 수 있어요.
strong.
강한.
it's your turn.
네 차례 야.
I also gamble at the bank.
나도 은행에서 도박을 한다.
How can we make the same bet?
어떻게 같은 내기를 할 수 있습니까?
If you want to keep it, you have to keep one too.
지키고 싶으면 하나쯤은 갖고 있어야지.
You're stupid, aren't you?
당신은 바보입니다, 그렇죠?
Where are the contrarian bets?
역배팅은 어디에 있나요?
besides,
게다가,
We must win together.
우리는 함께 승리해야 합니다.
If you lose, lose together.
잃으면 같이 지는 것이다.
It seems I can't
난 못할 것 같아
Can't leave you.
당신을 떠날 수 없습니다.
Open the card.
카드를 엽니다.
Relax a little, Zhuang.
좀 진정해, 좡.
The villagers are not small.
마을 사람들은 작지 않습니다.
It seems we are both very lucky
우리 둘 다 정말 운이 좋은 것 같아
Turning over is very difficult.
뒤집는 것은 매우 어렵습니다.
This is fate.
이것은 운명이다.
Ayo.
아요.
It's all over.
모든 끝났어.
Duane Resort hides this.
Duane Resort는 이를 숨깁니다.
camera.
카메라.
He monitors the whole process
그는 전체 과정을 모니터링합니다
Military headquarters.
군 본부.
Now,
지금,
We solve two problems.
우리는 두 가지 문제를 해결합니다.
First,
첫 번째,
how do we prevent
우리는 어떻게 방지합니까?
Was this video leaked?
이 영상 유출됐나요?
Want to touch Han Lie?
Han Lie를 만지고 싶나요?
second.
두번째.
Find this camera.
이 카메라를 찾아보세요.
Has Hangul been installed?
한글이 설치되어 있나요?
or
또는
other people?
다른 사람?
I think whoever installed the camera
내 생각엔 카메라를 설치한 사람이 누구든지
Not necessarily Han Lie.
반드시 한 거짓말은 아닙니다.
Through our previous investigation,
지난 조사를 통해,
he just
그는 그냥
Who sends the message.
메시지를 보내는 사람.
This research
이 연구
maybe not
아마
within a short period of time.
짧은 시간 안에.
Okay, turn it back first.
알았어, 먼저 다시 돌려봐
Let’s solve Han Lie’s problem first.
먼저 Han Lie의 문제를 해결해 보겠습니다.
OK
좋아요
Hangyeol’s report notes show
한결의 보고서 노트에는
A batch of fresh food will be delivered in the afternoon.
오후에는 신선한 음식이 배달됩니다.
Video images maybe
아마도 비디오 이미지
will be hidden inside and sent out.
내부에 숨겨져 발송됩니다.
In order to prevent the secret video from being spread,
비밀 영상이 유포되는 것을 방지하기 위해,
we must stop
우리는 멈춰야 해
Delivery of the Item.
품목 배송.
but...
하지만...
this traffic route
이 교통 경로
We have been paying attention for so long
우리는 오랫동안 관심을 기울여 왔습니다.
Grab it.
그것을 잡아.
A little reluctantly.
조금 마지 못해.
Can you do it?
당신은 그것을 할 수 있습니다?
so,
그래서,
we take advantage of this opportunity
우리는 이 기회를 이용한다
melalui Hangyeol.
멜라루이 한결.
we force it
우리는 그것을 강요
Boss Zhang is right behind him.
바로 뒤에 장보스가 있습니다.
If this video
만약 이 영상이
Unable to send
보낼 수 없습니다
from sea routes.
해상 노선에서.
Boss Zhang will definitely consider it
장 상사는 확실히 그것을 고려할 것입니다
Other methods.
다른 방법.
Submit this video.
이 동영상을 제출하세요.
so,
그래서,
We can catch more fish.
우리는 더 많은 물고기를 잡을 수 있습니다.
OK
좋아요
I called customs right away.
바로 세관에 전화했어요.
Prevent Han Lie from going to sea.
한리가 바다로 가는 것을 막으세요.
The system displays this item
시스템에 이 항목이 표시됩니다.
not approved.
승인이 거절 됨.
But when I give it to me
하지만 내가 그것을 나에게 주었을 때
Already approved.
이미 승인되었습니다.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
we can only
우리는 할 수
Based on system results.
시스템 결과를 기준으로 합니다.
An inspection was recently conducted.
최근 점검이 실시되었습니다.
This is your item
이것은 당신의 항목입니다
already taken.
이미 촬영되었습니다.
We have to check everything.
우리는 모든 것을 확인해야 합니다.
Send the cargo to the checkpoint.
화물을 검문소로 보내세요.
beautiful.
아름다운.
OK, thanks.
알았어 고마워.
He started looking for help.
그는 도움을 찾기 시작했습니다.
Let’s see how Boss Zhang handles it.
장보스가 어떻게 처리하는지 살펴보겠습니다.
Han Jie didn’t send this thing.
한지가 이런 걸 보내지 않았어요.
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Customs inspection.
세관 검사.
What a coincidence.
이런 우연이.
When we send the goods,
우리가 상품을 보낼 때,
I feel unusual.
기분이 이상해요.
Do you think there are people from Guoan behind this?
이 뒤에 Guoan 사람들이 있다고 생각하십니까?
There is such a possibility.
그런 가능성이 있습니다.
This line is very important to us.
이 라인은 우리에게 매우 중요합니다.
So, we have to leverage relationships.
그러므로 우리는 관계를 활용해야 합니다.
Find out what happened.
무슨 일이 일어났는지 알아보세요.
Halo?
후광?
Secretary Zheng, it’s me.
정 장관님, 나예요.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
That's it.
그게 다야.
have a friend
친구가 있어요
Let me ask something.
질문 좀 할게요.
piece of cake?
케이크 조각?
I think
제 생각에는
No need to bother the leader anymore.
더 이상 리더를 귀찮게 할 필요가 없습니다.
so,
그래서,
Ask him.
물어.
explain.
설명하다.
This friend of mine
이 친구는
There are many goods that are subject to customs inspection.
세관검사를 받는 물품이 많습니다.
I want to ask,
나는 묻고 싶다.
What is the specific reason?
구체적인 이유는 무엇입니까?
Send me the details.
세부정보를 보내주세요.
I will get back to you as soon as possible.
최대한 빨리 연락드리겠습니다.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Actually what?
실제로 무엇?
what exactly is it?
정확히 무엇입니까?
Have you never lost?
당신은 잃어버린 적이 없습니까?
If you lose, there are no secrets anymore.
잃으면 더 이상 비밀은 없습니다.
I'm thinking,
나는 생각 중입니다,
if you tell me
당신이 나에게 말하면
your secret,
당신의 비밀,
I'll tell you mine too.
내 것도 말해줄게.
Because you really keep your promise,
약속은 꼭 지키니까.
bet,
내기,
Forget it.
잊어 버려.
in this case,
이 경우,
what you really want to say
당신이 정말로 하고 싶은 말이 무엇인지
I would listen reluctantly.
나는 마지못해 듣곤 했다.
Forget it.
잊어 버려.
Did not you say
말하지 않았나요?
Is everything doomed?
모든 것이 운명인가?
Because we lost the bet,
우리가 내기에서 졌기 때문에,
maybe god
어쩌면 신이겠지
make it impossible for us
우리를 불가능하게 해
Sharing too many secrets with each other.
서로 비밀을 너무 많이 공유합니다.
correct.
옳은.
This is all fate.
이것은 모두 운명입니다.
So, let's save it first
그럼 먼저 저장해 볼까요?
The secret is in my heart.
그 비밀은 내 마음속에 있습니다.
to be honest.
솔직히 말하자면.
are you sorry
미안해요?
Want to play with me?
나랑 놀고 싶어?
if your partner is not me
네 파트너가 내가 아니라면
Neither will you
너도 마찬가지야
related to this issue.
이 문제와 관련이 있습니다.
regret.
후회.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
Why should I meet you?
내가 왜 당신을 만나야 합니까?
In the game?
게임에서?
if
만약에
Another way to meet,
또 다른 만남의 방법,
You won't be so unlucky now.
이제 당신은 그렇게 운이 좋지 않을 것입니다.
Don't think too much.
너무 많이 생각하지 마십시오.
What went wrong was the game.
문제가 된 것은 게임이었습니다.
Can't blame anyone.
누구도 비난할 수 없습니다.
besides,
게다가,
Even without you,
당신 없이도
I can't escape either.
나도 탈출할 수 없어요.
this game
이 게임
It is unknown how many people were injured.
얼마나 많은 사람이 다쳤는지는 알려지지 않았습니다.
As you said,
당신이 말했듯이,
Are we going back to play?
우리 다시 놀러 갈까?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Don’t we all agree?
우리 모두 동의하지 않나요?
Quit the game together?
함께 게임을 종료하시겠습니까?
what's on your mind?
무슨 생각 중이야?
I feel like he's
내 생각엔 그 사람이 그런 것 같아
A nightmare.
악몽.
appears sometimes.
가끔 나타납니다.
I can't help but think about it.
나는 그것에 대해 생각하지 않을 수 없습니다.
I always feel that this problem is definitely not solved.
나는 항상 이 문제가 확실히 해결되지 않았다고 느낀다.
Who are you,
누구세요,
So relaxing.
너무 편안해요.
Very relaxing.
매우 편안합니다.
Not playing games.
게임을 하지 않습니다.
like
좋다
There is no purpose.
목적이 없습니다.
Life has become very boring.
인생은 매우 지루해졌습니다.
Do you know why?
이유를 아시나요?
because of U.S
미국 때문에
In the game world.
게임 세계에서.
They are all gods.
그들은 모두 신이다.
But in the real world,
하지만 현실 세계에서는
Instead, it does nothing.
대신 아무것도 하지 않습니다.
Been playing this game for a long time.
오랫동안 이 게임을 해왔습니다.
Can't tell the difference anymore
더 이상 차이를 구분할 수 없습니다
Virtual and reality.
가상과 현실.
Have we been hit?
우리가 맞았나요?
Game poison?
게임 독?
what we lost
우리가 잃어버린 것
Not just a game,
게임뿐만 아니라,
But escape to another world.
하지만 다른 세계로 탈출하세요.
Give up your chance.
기회를 포기하세요.
Look at them.
저들을 봐.
They don't play.
그들은 놀지 않습니다.
They are still alive.
그들은 아직 살아있습니다.
as long as you can accept it
당신이 받아들일 수 있는 한
Boring life,
지루한 삶,
enough.
충분한.
in this case...
이 경우에는...
Not really.
설마.
Incidentally,
그런데,
Do you have any other goals?
다른 목표가 있나요?
or
또는
Or dream.
아니면 꿈.
There were a lot of people like that when I was a kid
나 어릴때 그런 사람 많았는데
When you grow up, you no longer have it.
당신이 자라면 더 이상 그것을 가질 수 없습니다.
my dream first
내 꿈이 먼저
Saving the world.
세상을 구합니다.
so?
그래서?
I realize now that I
이제 깨달았어 내가
Puzzled.
어찌할 바를 모르는.
More than 20 years later,
20여년이 지난 후,
Not only can I not save the world,
나는 세상을 구할 수 없을 뿐만 아니라,
I may still need
아직 필요할지도 몰라
Saved by this world.
이 세상이 구해줬어요.
I feel the same way.
나도 같은 느낌이다.
I'm very depressed now
나 지금 매우 우울해
You must use gambling to numb yourself.
자신을 무감각하게 만들려면 도박을 사용해야 합니다.
Use betting
베팅을 이용하세요
with bets.
베팅으로.
As you said,
당신이 말했듯이,
Do we want to live like this?
우리는 이렇게 살고 싶나요?
so?
그래서?
Can you really become Superman?
당신은 정말 슈퍼맨이 될 수 있나요?
Superman is definitely not.
슈퍼맨은 절대 아니다.
But at least,
하지만 적어도,
we can still do it
우린 아직 할 수 있어
Something meaningful.
의미있는 것.
For example?
예를 들어?
Just like now.
지금처럼.
You can do it first.
먼저 할 수 있습니다.
And try not to cause trouble to the country.
그리고 나라에 문제를 일으키지 않도록 노력하십시오.
And you?
당신은요?
What are your next plans?
다음 계획은 무엇입니까?
maybe one day
어쩌면 언젠가
I'm leaving Jinhai.
저는 진하이를 떠납니다.
where to?
어디로?
Back to Los Angeles.
로스앤젤레스로 돌아갑니다.
I didn't have any plans at first
처음에는 아무 계획도 없었어요
Stay in Jinhai.
진하이에 머물러 보세요.
It turns out you are in Jinhai
진하이에 계시는군요
for
~을 위한
mission accomplished.
임무 완수.
correct.
옳은.
In order to meet you,
당신을 만나기 위해서는,
Play games with you.
당신과 함께 게임을 즐겨보세요.
I know it's a lie
나는 그것이 거짓말이라는 것을 안다.
But I'm glad to hear it.
하지만 그 말을 들으니 기쁘네요.
You drank too much.
당신은 너무 많이 마셨다.
Not drunk.
취하지 않았습니다.
Have you ever heard a saying?
혹시라는 말을 들어본 적 있나요?
The more I realize it, the more ridiculous I find it.
깨달을수록 더 우스꽝스러워집니다.
I want
나는 원해요
Should I go back to racing?
다시 경주로 돌아가야 할까요?
No.
아니요.
Didn’t you just ban me?
방금 나를 차단하지 않았나요?
Bring this up?
이걸 올려?
Why do you say that yourself?
왜 스스로 그런 말을 하는 걸까요?
They deceived me.
그들은 나를 속였습니다.
I lost miserably.
나는 비참하게졌다.
Where did I lose?
내가 어디에서 잃었나요?
Where should I win?
어디서 이겨야 할까요?
You are really drunk.
당신 정말 취했어요.
you lose
당신은 잃습니다
At the casino.
카지노에서.
Not in the game.
게임에는 없습니다.
I don't mean money.
돈을 말하는 게 아닙니다.
so what?
그래서 뭐?
you.
너.
You are really drunk.
당신 정말 취했어요.
cheers.
건배.
No.
아니요.
as far as I know,
내가 아는 한,
Customs receives report
세관에서 신고 접수
Your store is suspected of smuggling.
당신의 가게는 밀수 혐의를 받고 있습니다.
smuggling?
밀수?
Who reported it?
누가 신고했나요?
Have you ever offended anyone?
누군가에게 기분을 상하게 한 적이 있나요?
No.
아니요.
Customs will be keeping a close eye on you these days.
요즘 세관에서 당신을 면밀히 감시할 것입니다.
For security reasons,
보안상의 이유로,
all tasks in this row
이 행의 모든 ​​작업
Stop first.
먼저 멈춰라.
We'll decide later.
나중에 결정하겠습니다.
Where is the cargo?
화물은 어디에 있나요?
I'll send someone to get it.
사람을 보내서 가져오도록 할게요.
and sent from another line.
다른 회선에서 전송되었습니다.
OK
좋아요
Hello, Director Huang.
안녕하세요, 황감독님.
Hello Hello hello.
안녕 안녕 안녕.
Welcome to Macau.
마카오에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
I'm also looking forward to it.
저도 기대하고 있어요.
this seminar.
이번 세미나.
Very good, very good, very good.
아주 좋아, 아주 좋아, 아주 좋아.
Please sit inside.
안쪽에 앉으세요.
OK
좋아요
Hang Lie leaves.
Hang Lie는 떠난다.
He went to church again.
그는 다시 교회에 갔다.
Most likely he accepted
아마도 그는 받아들였을 것이다.
New mission.
새로운 임무.
Do you think he's going to hand it over?
그 사람이 그것을 넘겨줄 것 같나요?
perhaps.
아마도.
Customs clearance cannot be carried out.
통관이 불가능합니다.
He must choose another path.
그는 다른 길을 선택해야 합니다.
Hope it will show up this time
이번엔 꼭 등장하길 바라
It's Boss Zhang.
장보스입니다.
Already arrived.
이미 도착했습니다.
Tuan Yu.
투안 유.
The laboratory has sent it
연구실에서 보냈어요
B13 ingredient analysis.
B13 성분 분석.
The B13 sample we got
우리가 얻은 B13 샘플
and the form of this composition
그리고 이 구성의 형태
All the same.
모두 같은.
But there are still some
그러나 아직 일부가 있습니다.
Slightly different.
약간 다른.
The difference is very small.
그 차이는 매우 작습니다.
We suspect this sample
우리는 이 샘플을 의심합니다
problem appear
문제가 나타남
there is a question.
질문이 있습니다.
Or he's not
아니면 그 사람이 아니거나
Latest research results.
최신 연구 결과.
OK, thanks.
알았어 고마워.
I received a sample of B13.
B13 샘플을 받았습니다.
there is a question.
질문이 있습니다.
Not a final sample.
최종 샘플이 아닙니다.
What do you think the problem is?
문제가 무엇이라고 생각하시나요?
The person who handles the sample,
샘플을 다루는 사람,
ada Yu Xiaoyue.
ada Yu Xiaoyue.
Shi Lei.
시 레이.
dan Han Jie.
단한지.
It can't be Yu Xiaoyue.
Yu Xiaoyue가 될 수는 없습니다.
He didn't get the original sample.
그는 원본 샘플을 얻지 못했습니다.
There was no reason for him to commit suicide.
그가 자살할 이유는 없었다.
Shi Leidan Han Jie
시 레이단 한 지에
Also a possibility
또한 가능성
Do something during transmission.
전송 중에 뭔가를 하십시오.
Shi Lei has already gone out.
Shi Lei는 이미 나갔습니다.
Han Jie is one of his own.
Han Jie는 자신의 사람 중 하나입니다.
He had no reason to take samples.
그는 샘플을 채취할 이유가 없었습니다.
Then sit quietly.
그런 다음 조용히 앉으십시오.
There is another possibility.
또 다른 가능성이 있습니다.
you mean,
네 말 뜻은,
What are the Gook-an people doing?
국안사람들은 뭐하고 있나요?
This is the worst case scenario.
이것은 최악의 시나리오입니다.
if this is true
이것이 사실이라면
Our transportation route is in Zhenhai
우리의 교통 경로는 Zhenhai에 있습니다.
most likely
아마도
under their supervision.
그들의 감독하에.
Han Lie's situation is very dangerous.
Han Lie의 상황은 매우 위험합니다.
National Security Agency.
국가 안보국.
He may have been watched.
그는 감시당했을 수도 있습니다.
You have to be careful.
조심해야합니다.
OK
좋아요
say.
말하다.
Han Lie was discovered.
한리(Han Lie)가 발견되었습니다.
He knows too much.
그는 너무 많은 것을 알고 있습니다.
It cannot fall into the hands of Guoan.
Guoan의 손에 넘어갈 수 없습니다.
Find a way to save it.
저장할 수 있는 방법을 찾으세요.
OK
좋아요
Halo?
후광?
You're caught.
당신은 잡혔습니다.
Someone is coming to pick you up. Come on.
누군가 당신을 데리러 올 거예요. 어서요.
Han Lie has already come down.
한리는 이미 내려왔습니다.
That motorcycle.
그 오토바이.
damaged.
손상되었습니다.
my car!
내 차!
stop!
멈추다!
He has already run away, so hurry up and chase him.
이미 도망갔으니 서둘러 쫓아가세요.
Ignore him for now.
지금은 그를 무시하세요.
Sooner or later you will catch it.
조만간 당신은 그것을 잡을 것입니다.
What about you, hard drive?
당신은 어떻습니까, 하드 드라이브?
I think my foot dropped.
발이 빠진 것 같아요.
Your head is dizzy, isn't it?
머리가 어지러워요?
A little dizzy.
약간 현기증이 난다.
Ayo.
아요.
This guy.
이 남자.
Is he Boss Zhang?
그 사람이 장 사장인가요?
Boss Zhang’s information,
장보스님의 정보,
He's a little fuzzy.
그 사람은 좀 멍청해요.
We can't be sure either.
우리도 확신할 수 없습니다.
He always wears a helmet.
그는 항상 헬멧을 착용합니다.
I can't see his face.
나는 그의 얼굴을 볼 수 없습니다.
I appreciate it.
감사합니다.
Wu Xi took the hard drive.
Wu Xi는 하드 드라이브를 가져갔습니다.
Why was Wu Xi injured?
우시가 부상당한 이유는 무엇입니까?
He's fine.
그는 괜찮아.
Now.
지금.
Under examination at the hospital.
병원에서 검사중입니다.
Di mana Hangyeol?
디마나 한결?
Now is our only clue.
이제 유일한 단서입니다.
we have to find a way
우리는 방법을 찾아야 해
Find it.
그것을 찾아라.
of.
의.
We were at his place.
우리는 그의 집에있었습니다.
and Tuna King Shop.
그리고 참치킹샵.
Everyone is looking at him.
모두가 그를보고 있습니다.
OK
좋아요
game account
게임 계정
Still there too
아직도 거기도 있어
within our regulatory scope.
규제 범위 내에서.
As long as he comes in,
그 사람이 들어오는 한,
We'll find out.
우리가 알아낼 것입니다.
Also, check him out.
또한 그를 확인해보세요.
All online transaction records.
모든 온라인 거래 기록.
see if we can
우리가 할 수 있는지 알아봐
Find his hiding place.
그의 은신처를 찾아보세요.
You are like ports and docks.
당신은 항구와 부두와 같습니다.
This all needs investigation.
이 모든 것은 조사가 필요합니다.
He knows this area very well.
그는 이 분야를 아주 잘 알고 있다.
The main investigation concerns him.
주요 조사는 그에 관한 것입니다.
with him.
그와 함께.
Fishermen and traders.
어부와 상인.
Chief Qin.
진 수석.
This operation failed.
이 작업은 실패했습니다.
I have a great responsibility.
나는 큰 책임을 가지고 있습니다.
Your choice is correct.
당신의 선택은 정확합니다.
I would do the same thing.
나도 같은 일을 할 것입니다.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
besides,
게다가,
who installed
누가 설치했는가
Who installed it?
누가 설치했나요?
Inside the Duane Hotel.
듀에인 호텔 내부.
most likely
아마도
A spy has infiltrated.
스파이가 침입했습니다.
this line.
이 줄.
You should continue to investigate.
계속해서 조사해야 합니다.
understand.
이해하다.
Yao Yao.
야오야오.
Are you awake?
깨어있나요?
I have a headache.
두통이 있어요.
Drink water first.
먼저 물을 마셔보세요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
do you remember
기억 나니
What did you say to me yesterday?
어제 나한테 뭐라고 했어?
What?
무엇?
your secret.
당신의 비밀.
What secret?
무슨 비밀이요?
explain.
설명하다.
Do you want to get back into the game?
게임에 다시 참여하시겠습니까?
What else did I tell you?
내가 또 뭐라고 말했지?
what else?
또 뭐야?
Contribute to the country.
국가에 기여하십시오.
Isn't this a mistake?
이건 실수 아닌가요?
play games.
게임을하다.
what is the relationship
무슨 관계야?
Contribute to the country?
국가에 기여한다?
Who knows what you mean?
무슨 말인지 누가 알겠어요?
We'll meet again.
우리는 다시 만날 거에요.
Our flagship agency.
우리의 대표 에이전시.
We're all out.
우리는 모두 끝났습니다.
in life,
인생에서,
There are always some things that cannot be done.
할 수 없는 일이 항상 존재합니다.
this is your room
여기가 당신의 방입니다
too small.
너무 작은.
I'll change it for you to a bigger one.
더 큰 것으로 바꿔드릴게요.
unnecessary.
불필요한.